Contact

4042466171 (Mobile) cisriopenn@yahoo.com

www.linkedin.com/in/deborah-lewis-rn-15465028 (LinkedIn)

Top Skills

Nursing Healthcare

BLS

Languages

English

DEBORAH LEWIS, RN

CCRN at Grady Health System

Atlanta, Georgia

Summary

Experienced Registered Nurse with a demonstrated history of working in the hospital & health care industry. Skilled in Tracheostomy, Medical-Surgical, Medication Administration, Palliative Care, and Geriatric Nursing. Strong healthcare services professional with a Associate's Degree focused in Registered Nursing/Registered Nurse from Darton College.

Experience

Grady Health System 4 years 4 months

CCRN

August 2017 - Present (3 years)

Greater Atlanta Area

Registered Nurse
April 2016 - Present (4 years 4 months)

Atlanta

Med Surg Nurse

Signature Healthcare of Marietta Charge Nurse May 2014 - April 2016 (2 years)

Marietta, Georgia

Responsible for the direct care of clients. Under the direction of the Nurse Manager and Physician, providing prescribed care. Assessed clients and administered medication, within my scope of practice. Responsible for the direct supervision of the nursing assistant on my assigned shift. Developed and managed nursing care plans while instructing patients and their families in proper treatment. Assisted individuals and groups towards improving or maintaining health.

Tower Road Health Charge Nurse

April 2013 - April 2014 (1 year 1 month)

Responsible for the direct care of clients. Under the direction of the Nurse Manager and Physician, providing prescribed care. Assessed clients and administered medication, within my scope of practice. Responsible for the direct supervision of the nursing assistant on my assigned shift. Developed and managed nursing care plans while instructing patients and their families in proper treatment. Assisted individuals and groups towards improving or maintaining health.

Cobb Douglas Board Of Health Infirmary Nurse August 2007 - December 2011 (4 years 5 months) Marietta, Georgia

Functioned under direction of the Registered Nurse. Worked within the LPN Scope of Practice to assist in providing patient care. Assessed clients and administered medication, as well as instruct patients in proper education and treatment needs. Helping individuals take steps to improve or maintain health.

Noreen Mc Keen Residence CHARGE NURSE January 2004 - August 2005 (1 year 8 months) West Palm Beach, Florida

Responsible for the direct care of clients. Under the direction of the Nurse Manager and Physician, providing prescribed care. Assessed clients and administered medication, within my scope of practice. Responsible for the direct supervision of the nursing assistant on my assigned shift. Developed and managed nursing care plans while instructing patients and their families in proper treatment. Assisted individuals and groups towards improving or maintaining health.

Education

Columbus State University

Bachelor of Science - BS, Registered Nursing, Nursing Administration, Nursing Research and Clinical Nursing · (2017 - 2018)

Darton College

Associate's Degree, Registered Nursing/Registered Nurse · (2014 - 2015)

Chattahoochee Technical College

Associate of Science (AS), Registered Nursing/Registered Nurse · (2011 - 2014)

Academy for Practical Nursing & Health Occupations
Licensed Practical Nurse, Adult Health Nurse/Nursing · (2002 - 2003)